A Guide to the Virginia Room Vertical and Historic Landmark Files, Undated
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Upper Potomac
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Planning Districts - Vienna
- VF - Fx. Co. - Planning & Zoning - Difficult Run Watershed
- VF - Fx. Co. - Poverty
- VF - Fx. Co. - Public Works
- VF - Fx. Co. - Taxes
- VF - Fx. Co. - Tourism
- HLF - Gabrielson Gardens - - Oakton
- VF - Gambling
- HLF - Garden Apartments - Fairfax Co & Montgomery Co MD - 1930 - 1955
- VF - Genealogy - Consanguinity
- VF - Genealogy - Forms
- VF - Genealogy - Melungeons
- VF - Geology
- HLF - Ghosts
- HLF - Gooding's Tavern
- HLF - Grandview
- HLF - Grand-View-on-the-Potomac
- HLF - Gray's Hill
- HLF - Great Falls - History - (1 of 2)
- HLF - Great Falls - History - (2 of 2)
- HLF - Great Falls - Matildaville
- HLF - Great Falls - Patowmack Canal
- HLF - Great Falls Grange
- HLF - Great Oaks (Whiston House) - 8234 Citadel Place - Vienna
- HLF - Green Spring Farm
- HLF - Greenway Court
- HLF - Greenway Downs
- HLF - Grey Gables
- HLF - Grigsby House
- HLF - Groveton
- HLF - Groveton - History
- HLF - Grubisich "Gingerbread" House (Reston, Va.).
- HLF - Gum Springs - History
- HLF - Gunnell (John) House - Arnon Meadow Road - Dranesville
- HLF - Gunnell House
- HLF - Gunnell's Run
- HLF - Gunston Hall (1 of 3)
- HLF - Gunston Hall (2 of 3)
- HLF - Gunston Hall (3 of 3)
- HLF - Gunston Manor - - Mason Neck
- HLF - Gypsies
- HLF - Habitat for Humanity Houses
- HLF - Hall Estate House - Park Pointe - 7407 Gambrill Road
- HLF - Halley Properties - Ox Road - Lorton
- VF - Handicapped
- HLF - Hantslot - Newman Road - Clifton
- HLF - Havener House - See: Centreville-Havener House
- HLF - Hayfield
- HLF - Hayfield Barn
- HLF - Head's Hill Farm
- VF - Health - Diseases
- VF - Health Systems Agency of Northern Virginia
- VF - Heraldry Scams
- HLF - Hermitage
- HLF - Herndon - Chamber of Commerce
- HLF - Herndon - Cooktown
- HLF - Herndon - Fire (1917)
- HLF - Herndon - Gas Plant
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (1961-1965)
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (1966-1970)
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (1971-1975)
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (1976-1980)
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (1981-1985)
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (1986-1990)
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (1991-1995)
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (1996-2000)
- HLF - Herndon - Government - (2001 & Later)
- HLF - Herndon - Herndon College
- HLF - Herndon - Historic District
- HLF - Herndon - Historic Homes
- HLF - Herndon - History
- HLF - Herndon - Kitchen Cottage
- HLF - Herndon - Margaret Thomas' Garden - (Iris Lady)
- HLF - Herndon - Officials
- HLF - Herndon - Payne/Yount House
- HLF - Herndon - Police
- HLF - Herndon - Post Office
- HLF - Herndon - Railroad Station
- HLF - Herndon - Restaurants
- HLF - Herndon - Riot (1974)
- HLF - Herndon - S.S. Central America
- HLF - Herndon - Town Hall
- HLF - Herndon - Yellow House
- HLF - Hickory Hill
- HLF - Hidden Springs Farm
- HLF - Hideaway Park Subdivision
- HLF - Highland View
- HLF - Hillsville Massacre, Carroll Co., Va. - (Fairfax County Jurors)
- HLF - Hillwood
- HLF - Hillwood Square
- HLF - Historic Preservation
- HLF - Historic Preservation - Historic Districts
- HLF - Historic Preservation - Historic Landmarks Survey
- HLF - Historic Preservation - Houses - Architectural Research
- HLF - Hitaffer Road
- HLF - Hitchcock Toll House
- HLF - Holden Houses Elsinore - Ordway Road
- VF - Holidays
- VF - Holidays - Christmas
- VF - Holidays - Martin Luther King
- VF - Holidays - Thanksgiving
- HLF - Hollin Hall
- HLF - Hollin Hills Subdivision
- HLF - Holly Hill
- HLF - Holly Knoll - Bloomfield
- HLF - Holly Knoll Subdivision
- HLF - Hollywood Farm
- HLF - Holmes Run Acres Subdivision
- VF - Homelessness
- HLF - Homestead Exemption - - 1860s
- HLF - Hope Park
- HLF - Hope Park Mill
- HLF - Hope Park Mill Miller's House
- VF - Hospice Care
- VF - Hospitals
- VF - Hospitals - Alexandria
- VF - Hospitals - Arlington
- VF - Hospitals - Centreville
- VF - Hospitals - Commonwealth
- VF - Hospitals - Fair Oaks
- VF - Hospitals - Fairfax
- VF - Hospitals - Fairfax Hospital Association
- VF - Hospitals - Jefferson
- VF - Hospitals - Mount Vernon
- VF - Hospitals - Northern Virginia Doctors
- VF - Hospitals - Reston
- HLF - Hot Shoppes
- HLF - Houses - History-How to
- HLF - Huchison (John) House - Pleasant Valley Road - Sully
- VF - Humor
- HLF - Hunter House (Nottoway Park) - see Dandru Farm
- HLF - Hunter Mill Road (#1442) - - Dranesville
- HLF - Hunter's Lodge
- VF - Hunting & Shooting
- HLF - Hunting Creek
- HLF - Huntingdon
- HLF - Huntington
- HLF - Huntington Metro Area
- HLF - Huntley
- VF - Hunts & Hunting
- VF - Hunts & Hunting - Bull Run Hunt
- VF - Hunts & Hunting - Fairfax Hunt
- VF - Hunts & Hunting - Pohick Valley
- HLF - Hutchison, Jeremiah House
- HLF - Hutchison, Silas - Saw and Gristmill Dam and Ruins
- HLF - Hutchison, Silas House
- HLF - Hybla Valley
- HLF - Hybla Valley Speedway - - Alexandria
- HLF - ILDA
- HLF - Indian Spring Farm
- HLF - Indians
- HLF - Innisfail
- VF - Insects
- HLF - Ivakota Farm (Clifton, Va.).
- HLF - Ivy Chimney
- HLF - Jackson (Jennie) House - River Bend Road - Great Falls
- HLF - Jackson (Verlinda) House - 700 River Bend Road - Upper Potomac
- HLF - Jackson House (Great Falls, Va.).
- HLF - Jamestown - 400th Anniversary
- HLF - Jamestown - 400th Anniversay - McLean / Great Falls
- HLF - Jasper Property (Fairfax Station, Va.).
- HLF - Jefferson Village Apartments
- HLF - Jones House - (see Maple Hill)
- HLF - Jurgensen House (Alexandria, Va.).
- HLF - Kalorama Springs - (Tricketts')
- HLF - Kelsey Cabin
- HLF - Kenmore
- HLF - Kenmore Post Office
- HLF - Kent Road (#7907) - - Alexandria
- HLF - Keyes House
- HLF - King Subdivision - Elizabeth Street - Upper Potomac
- HLF - Kings Grant (Burke, Va.).
- HLF - Kings Park Subdivision
- HLF - Kingstowne
- HLF - Kirkside [Subdivision]
- HLF - Kreuttner Mansion
- HLF - Ku Klux Klan
- HLF - La Grange (Lorton, Va.).
- HLF - Lahey House
- HLF - Lake Anne Village Center
- HLF - Lake Barcroft Dam (Falls Church, Va.).
- HLF - Lamb House
- HLF - Lamond House - 7509 Fort Hunt Road - Alexandria
- HLF - Lane's Mill (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Langley Area - History
- HLF - Langley Hall - Stormbrook - McLean, VA
- HLF - Langley Mansion House (Langley, Va.).
- HLF - Langley Ordinary (Langley, Va.).
- HLF - Langley Toll House (Langley, Va.).
- HLF - Laurel Grove School (Franconia, Va.).
- HLF - Laurel Hill (Lorton, Va.). - the house, not the area
- HLF - Laurel Hill Master Plan
- HLF - Lazy Susan Dinner Theatre
- HLF - Leary School - Pixieland School - 6349-6353 Lincolnia Road
- HLF - Lebanon (Lorton, Va.).
- HLF - Leeton (Lee)
- HLF - Leeton (Turberville) - 4619 Walney Road - Bull Run
- HLF - Leigh (Vernon) House - 9352 Mildred Court - Great Falls
- HLF - Leigh House
- HLF - Leiter Estate (McLean, Va.).
- HLF - Level Green Farm
- HLF - Leven Preserve
- HLF - LeVine House
- HLF - Lewinsville Area - History
- HLF - Lewinsville House
- HLF - Lewinsville Post Office
- HLF - Lewis/Oliver House (McLean, Va.). - Mackall Cabin - 1032 Towlston Road
- HLF - Lexington (Lorton, Va.).
- VF - Libraries - (1960-1963)
- VF - Libraries - (1964-1967)
- VF - Libraries - (1968-1969)
- VF - Libraries - (1970-1971)
- VF - Libraries - (1972-1973)
- VF - Libraries - (1974)
- VF - Libraries - (1975)
- VF - Libraries - (1976)
- VF - Libraries - (1977)
- VF - Libraries - (1978)
- VF - Libraries - (1979)
- VF - Libraries - (1980-1989)
- VF - Libraries - (1990-1999)
- VF - Libraries - (2000-2009)
- VF - Libraries - (2010-)
- VF - Libraries - (Pre-1960)
- VF - Libraries - 1989 - 50th Anniversary
- VF - Libraries - Automation
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Burke Centre Mini
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Carter Glass
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Central (1962-1982)
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Centreville
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Chantilly
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Dolly Madison
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Engleside
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Fair Oaks Mini
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Fairfax City Regional (1983-2003)
- VF - Libraries - Branches - George Mason
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Great Falls
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Herndon Fortnightly
- VF - Libraries - Branches - John Marshall
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Kings Park
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Kingstowne
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Lorton
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Martha Washington
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Oakton
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Patrick Henry
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Pohick
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Reston
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Richard Byrd
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Sherwood
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Thomas Jefferson
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Tysons-Pimmit
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Woodrow Wilson
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Burke Regional
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Fairfax City Regional (2004- )
- VF - Libraries - Branches - Hunters Woods Mini
- VF - Libraries - Censorship
- VF - Libraries - Censorship - Washington Blade
- VF - Libraries - Censorship - Internet
- VF - Libraries - Employees
- VF - Libraries - Employees - Comparable Worth Suit
- VF - Libraries - Employees - Pay and Classification Plans (Salary)
- VF - Libraries - Friends Organizations
- VF - Libraries - Library Board
- VF - Libraries - Outreach Programs - Incl. Bookmobiles, Access Services, etc…
- VF - Libraries - Special Collections - Business & Technology
- VF - Libraries - Special Collections - Music Collection
- VF - Libraries - Special Collections - Virginia Room
- VF - Libraries - Special Collections - Media Services
- HLF - Limewood
- HLF - Lincolnia - History
- HLF - Lincoln-Lewis-Vannoy Sanitary Sewer
- HLF - Little Falls
- HLF - Little Hollin Hall
- HLF - Little Sully
- HLF - Log Cabins
- HLF - London Towne Subdivision
- HLF - Longacre - 701 Seneca Road - Dranesville
- HLF - Longview
- HLF - Lorton - History - (1 of 2)
- HLF - Lorton - History - (2 of 2)
- HLF - Lorton - Lorton Brick Factory
- HLF - Lorton - Springman House - 9310 Gunston Cove Road
- HLF - Lowland Station
- HLF - Lundy House
- HLF - Mackall House
- HLF - Mackall-Hall House - McLean - 1011 Turkey Run Road
- HLF - Madeira School - - Dranesville
- VF - Magazines - Northern Virginia
- HLF - Mantua
- HLF - Maple Hill
- HLF - Maplewood (Tysons Corner, Va.).
- HLF - Marmota Farm - Great Falls
- VF - Marriage Equality
- HLF - Marsden House
- HLF - Marshall House (Burke, Va.).
- HLF - Martin House - 2400 Sandburg St., Dunn Loring, Va.
- HLF - Mason (Otis Tufton) House - 8907 Richmond Highway - Mount Vernon
- HLF - Mason Boundary Stones (Lorton, Va.).
- VF - Mason Hirst Research Institute
- HLF - Mason's Neck (Lorton, Va.). - (1 of 2)
- HLF - Mason's Neck (Lorton, Va.). - (2 of 2)
- HLF - Massey Building
- HLF - Matildaville - (see Great Falls - Matildaville)
- HLF - Maury
- HLF - Mayfield
- HLF - McDaniel Home - - Herndon
- HLF - McLean - (1950-1965)
- HLF - McLean - (1966-1970)
- HLF - McLean - (1971-1980)
- HLF - McLean - (1981-1990)
- HLF - McLean - (1991-2000)
- HLF - McLean - (2001-2010)
- HLF - McLean - Bank's Home Bombing (1974)
- HLF - Mclean - Commons of McLean
- HLF - McLean - Crest Lane [Subdivision]
- HLF - McLean - Crest Lane [Subdivision] Edgecomb
- HLF - McLean - Federal Highway Administration Time Capsule
- HLF - McLean - Federal Highway Administration Time Capsule
- HLF - McLean - Half-House
- HLF - McLean - Historic Homes
- HLF - McLean - History
- HLF - McLean - Laughlin House
- HLF - McLean - LeFrak House
- HLF - McLean - McLean Central Park
- HLF - McLean - McLean Citizens Assoc./Citizens Council
- HLF - McLean - McLean Community Center
- HLF - McLean - McLean Hamlet [Subdivision]
- HLF - McLean - Minor's Hill
- HLF - McLean - Post Office
- HLF - McLean - Roads
- HLF - McLean - Springhouse - (Linway Terrace)
- HLF - McLean - Storm Farm
- HLF - McLean - Ted Kennedy House
- HLF - McLean - Town Status
- HLF - McMillen Farm
- HLF - Meadowlark Gardens
- HLF - Meat House
- HLF - Merrifield Area - History
- HLF - Merrybrook (Herndon, Va.).
- HLF - Merry-Go-Round (Vienna, Va.).
- HLF - Merryhill
- HLF - Merrywood
- HLF - Metzer House (Colchester, Va.).
- HLF - Middleton Farm (Henrdon, Va.).
- HLF - Mills - History
- HLF - Minnick House - Old Colchester Road - Lorton
- VF - Minorities
- VF - Minorities - Hispanic
- VF - Minorities - Korean
- VF - Minorities - Vietnamese
- HLF - Mitchell-Weeks House (Chantilly, Va.).
- HLF - Mohler House (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Moidone (Vienna, Va.).
- HLF - Moorefield (Vienna, Va.).
- HLF - Mosby's Rock (Herndon, Va.).
- VF - Motor Vehicles
- HLF - Mount (Falls Church, Va.).
- HLF - Mount Air (Newington, Va.).
- HLF - Mount Auburn
- HLF - Mount Eagle
- HLF - Mount Erin
- HLF - Mount Gilead (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Mount Pleasant - Telegraph Road - Alexandria
- HLF - Mount Pleasant (Falls Church, Va.).
- HLF - Mount Vernon (Mount Vernon, Va.). - (1 of 5)
- HLF - Mount Vernon (Mount Vernon, Va.). - (2 of 5)
- HLF - Mount Vernon (Mount Vernon, Va.). - (3 of 5)
- HLF - Mount Vernon (Mount Vernon, Va.). - (4 of 5)
- HLF - Mount Vernon (Mount Vernon, Va.). - (5 of 5)
- HLF - Mount Vernon Area - History
- HLF - Mountain View (Centreville, Va.). - (1 of 2)
- HLF - Mountain View (Centreville, Va.). - (2 of 2)
- HLF - Moutoux Orchard (Vienna, Va.).
- HLF - Movie Theatres
- HLF - Mulberry Hill
- HLF - Mullins House
- HLF - Munson Hill
- HLF - Murtaugh Farm (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Myths & Legends - "Chessie"
- HLF - Myths & Legends - Beale Treasure
- HLF - Myths & Legends - Braddocks Gold
- HLF - Myths & Legends - Bunny Man
- HLF - Myths & Legends - Ghosts - FX
- HLF - Myths & Legends - Ghosts - VA
- HLF - Myths & Legends - Mount Vernon Monster
- HLF - Myths & Legends - Treasure Legends
- HLF - Myths & Legends - U. F. O.'s
- HLF - Navy Area - History
- HLF - New Alexandria (Alexandria, Va.).
- HLF - Newington Area
- HLF - Newington Railroad Station (Newington, Va.).
- VF - Newspapers - Alexandria Gazette
- VF - Newspapers - Arlington Catholic Herald
- VF - Newspapers - Chronicle Newspapers
- VF - Newspapers - Connection Newspapers
- VF - Newspapers - Fairfax City Times
- VF - Newspapers - Fairfax Herald
- VF - Newspapers - Free Press and Sun Echo
- VF - Newspapers - Globe Newspapers
- VF - Newspapers - Journal Newspapers
- VF - Newspapers - Northern Virginia area
- VF - Newspapers - Observer Newspapers
- VF - Newspapers - Providence Journal
- VF - Newspapers - Reston Times
- VF - Newspapers - Sun Newspapers
- VF - Newspapers - The Market Place
- VF - Newspapers - The Washington Examiner
- VF - Newspapers - Times Community Newspapers
- VF - Newspapers - Virginia Sentinel
- HLF - Newton Boundary Stone (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Newton's Mill Ruins (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Nike Missile Sites
- HLF - Nipper the Dog (RCA Victor)
- HLF - Nonimportation Broadside - (See: Virginia Nonimportation Assoc. Broadside)
- HLF - Northcrest
- VF - Northern Virginia Planning District Commission
- VF - Northern Virginia Recreation and Cultural Auth.
- VF - Northern Virginia Soil & Water Cons. Dist.
- HLF - Nudist Camps
- HLF - Oak Grove
- HLF - Oak Hill (Annandale, Va.).
- HLF - Oakley (Fairfax, Va.).
- HLF - Oakton - Bannockburn
- HLF - Oakton - Fort Flint
- HLF - Oakton - History
- HLF - Oakton - Oak Trees
- HLF - Oakton - Post Office
- HLF - Oakton - Trolley Station
- VF - Occoquan Watershed - - see also: Water Supply
- HLF - Occoquan Workhouse
- HLF - Odrick [Alfred] Farmstead (McLean, Va.).
- HLF - Odrick's Corner Area - History
- HLF - Okeley
- HLF - Old Dominion Drive (#7527)
- HLF - Old Well Road (#4908)
- HLF - Orchard Hill (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Orchard Spring
- HLF - Ossian Hall (Annandale, Va.).
- HLF - Othman House
- HLF - Overlook
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Annandale Community
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Bryant Farm
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Burke Lake
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Clemyjontri
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Dunn Loring Community
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Eleanor C. Lawrence
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Frying Pan Farm
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - George Washington Recreation Center
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Hidden Pond Nature Center
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Huntley Meadows
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Jefferson District
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Lake Accotink
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Lake Fairfax
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Lee District
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Long Branch
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Martin Luther King, Jr.
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Mason District
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Mount Vernon District
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Nottoway
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Pinecrest Golf Course
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Riverbend
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Scott's Run
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Wakefield Recreation Center
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co.
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - (1959-1969)
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - (1970-1979)
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - (1980-1989)
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - (1990-later)
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - (A thru K)
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - (L thru Z)
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Cub Run Rec Center
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Mason Neck State Park
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Cross County Trail
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - White Horticultural Park
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Sully Woodlands
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Ox Hill Park
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Great Falls Park
- VF - Parks - Fairfax Co. - Langley Fork Park
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg.
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Algonkian
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Bull Run Marina
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Bull Run Regional
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Cameron Run
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Hemlock Overlook
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Meadowlark Gardens
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Pohick Bay
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Potomac Overlook
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Red Rock Wilderness Overlook
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Sandy Run
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Upton Hill
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - Fountainhead
- VF - Parks - No. Va. Reg. - W. & O. D. Railroad
- VF - Parks - U.S. National Park Service - Dyke Marsh
- VF - Parks - U.S. National Park Service - The Mall
- HLF - Patowmack Dairy Farm (Great Falls, Va.). - (Spaulding Farm)
- HLF - Patton House
- HLF - Peacock House - (Peacock Station)
- HLF - Pender Area - History
- HLF - Penn-Daw Area - History
- HLF - Pig n' Chic (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Pimmit Hills Subdivision (Falls Church, Va.).
- HLF - Pine Spring Subdivision
- HLF - Pioneer Grange Hall (Annandale, Va.).
- HLF - Piscataway Farm
- HLF - Place Names - Fairfax County
- HLF - Plantation
- HLF - Pohick Tobacco Warehouse (Colchester, Va.). - (c. 1732)
- VF - Police - (1966)
- VF - Police - (1967)
- VF - Police - (1968)
- VF - Police - (1969)
- VF - Police - (1970)
- VF - Police - (1971)
- VF - Police - (1972)
- VF - Police - (1973)
- VF - Police - (1974)
- VF - Police - (1975)
- VF - Police - (1976)
- VF - Police - (1977)
- VF - Police - (1978)
- VF - Police - (1979)
- VF - Police - (1980 & later)
- VF - Police - (Pre-1966)
- VF - Police - 911 System
- VF - Police - CIA Scandal (1975)
- VF - Police - Helicoptor Unit
- VF - Police - No. Va. Criminal Justice Academy
- VF - Police - Park Police
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Annandale
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Chantilly
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Fair Oaks
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Franconia
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Groveton
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Mason
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - McLean
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Mount Vernon
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Reston
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - Sully
- VF - Police - Sub-Stations - West Springfield
- VF - Police - Unions
- VF - Police - Virginia State Police
- HLF - Poor Houses (Poor Farm)
- HLF - Pope-Leighey House (Woodlawn, Va.).
- HLF - Popkins Farm (Alexandria, Va.).
- HLF - Poplar Tree Estates
- VF - Population - 2000-
- VF - Population (1950's)
- VF - Population (1960's)
- VF - Population (1970's)
- VF - Population (1980's)
- VF - Population (1990's)
- VF - Population (pre-1950s)
- HLF - Post Offices - Fairfax County
- HLF - Poston House (Reston, Va.).
- HLF - Potomac House
- HLF - Potomac River Gun
- HLF - Pre-Fabricated Housing
- HLF - Prices Ordinary
- HLF - PRISONER-OF-WAR Camps in Fairfax County
- VF - Prisons - Lorton Prison - (1973)
- VF - Prisons - Lorton Prison - (1974)
- VF - Prisons - Lorton Prison - (1975)
- VF - Prisons - Lorton Prison - (1976-1980)
- VF - Prisons - Lorton Prison - (1981-1983)
- VF - Prisons - Lorton Prison - (1984-1990)
- VF - Prisons - Lorton Prison - (1991 & Later)
- VF - Prisons - Lorton Prison - (Pre-1972)
- VF - Prisons - Virginia - Camp 30
- HLF - Prospect Hill (Langley, Va.).
- HLF - Quailwood (Clifton, Va.).
- HLF - Quigg House (Clifton, Va.).
- VF - Radio
- VF - Radon
- VF - Railroads - Auto Train
- VF - Railroads - Centreville Military Railroad
- VF - Railroads - Commuter Rail - (1961-1979)
- VF - Railroads - Dulles Area Rapid Transit (DART)
- VF - Railroads - Great Falls and Old Dominion
- VF - Railroads - Lorton & Occoquan Railroad
- VF - Railroads - Manassas Gap
- VF - Railroads - Orange and Alexandria Railroad Historical Trail
- VF - Railroads - Potomac Yard
- VF - Railroads - Richmond, Fredericksburg, & Potomac
- VF - Railroads - Southern Railway
- VF - Railroads - Trolley Lines
- VF - Railroads - Virginia Railway Express - (1985 & later)
- VF - Railroads - Washington and Old Dominion
- VF - Railroads - Washington, Alexandria and Mount Vernon Railway
- HLF - Rambler Articles
- HLF - Ramshorn Place (#6115) - - Langley
- HLF - Ranleigh
- HLF - Ratcliffe-Hanna House - (See: Merrybrook)
- HLF - Ravensworth (Springfield, Va.).
- HLF - Ravensworth Farm Subdivision (Springfield, Va.).
- HLF - Red Hill (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Reid's Store (Fairfax Station, Va.).
- HLF - Reston - (1960-1965)
- HLF - Reston - (1966)
- HLF - Reston - (1967-1969)
- HLF - Reston - (1970-1972)
- HLF - Reston - (1973-1975)
- HLF - Reston - (1976-1978)
- HLF - Reston - (1979-1984)
- HLF - Reston - (1985-1989)
- HLF - Reston - (1990-2000)
- HLF - Reston - (2001-2010)
- HLF - Reston - (2011-2020)
- HLF - Reston - API Building (American Press Institute Building)
- HLF - Reston - Cameron Glen Care Center
- HLF - Reston - Civic Groups - (includes RHOA)
- HLF - Reston - Colonial Pipeline Spill (1993)
- HLF - Reston - Dams
- HLF - Reston - Dams - Lake Anne
- HLF - Reston - Dams - Lake Audobon
- HLF - Reston - Dams - Lake Newport
- HLF - Reston - Dams - Lake Thoreau
- HLF - Reston - Embry Rucker Shelter
- HLF - Reston - GRACE
- HLF - Reston - Historic Homes
- HLF - Reston - History
- HLF - Reston - Hunters Woods
- HLF - Reston - Lake Anne Community Center
- HLF - Reston - Lake Anne Village - 1965-1990
- HLF - Reston - Lake Anne Village - 1991-
- HLF - Reston - Reston Community Center
- HLF - Reston - Reston International Center
- HLF - Reston - Reston Museum
- HLF - Reston - Reston Music Center
- HLF - Reston - Reston Nature Center
- HLF - Reston - Reston Pet Farm
- HLF - Reston - Reston Town Center
- HLF - Reston - Roads
- HLF - Reston - Sambos Restaurant (1977)
- HLF - Reston - Schools
- HLF - Reston - Town Status
- HLF - Reston - United States Geological Survey
- HLF - Retirement - (See: Stoneybrooke)
- HLF - River Farm (Mount Vernon, Va.).
- VF - Rivers - Potomac River - Potomac River Basin
- VF - Rivers - Potomac River - History
- VF - Rivers - Potomac River - Hydrilla
- VF - Rivers - Potomac River - Water Quality
- VF - Rivers - Potomac River - Brochures
- VF - Roads - (1966-1970)
- VF - Roads - (1971-1975)
- VF - Roads - (1976-1980)
- VF - Roads - (1981-1985)
- VF - Roads - (1985-1990)
- VF - Roads - (Pre-1966)
- VF - Roads - Backlick Rd.
- VF - Roads - Braddock Rd.
- VF - Roads - Chain Bridge Rd. (Rte. 123)
- VF - Roads - Clifton Rd.
- VF - Roads - Columbia Pike